[Music]
[Música]
Well there's one thing I had to
y Bueno hay una cosa Que que os tenía
tell you too okay I haven't been
que comentar también vale no lo he
able to promote it well because uh
podido promocionar bien porque eh lo
we did it on I don't know if Tuesday or
hicimos el no sé si el martes o el
Wednesday Wednesday we were with
miércoles el miércoles estuvimos con
Marinilla and Thursday yesterday we were with
marinilla y el jueves ayer estuvimos con
El Corrillo So no no here on
el Corrillo Entonces no no aquí en
telesalseo I haven't been able to
telesalseo no os lo he podido
promote it well but I have
promocionar bien pero sí que lo he
promoted it well with La Salsería with
promocionado bien con la salsería con
the kids okay we have created
los chavales vale hemos creado de
reinforcement okay as a spare
refuerzo vale de repuesto
let's say on Facebook I have created the
digamos en Facebook me he creado los
same channels Okay you can
mismos canales Okay ustedes podéis
continue watching it because I do
seguir viendo lo lo porque esto yo aquí
n't monetize here I mean on Facebook for
no monetizas O sea en Facebook para que
you to get monetization you have to
te den la monetización eso tienes que
be I know Auron Play and I think you
ser yo que sé auron Play y creo que
monetize two bucks you know I mean it's
monetizas dos duros me entiendes O sea
not worth it for me Facebook what I
no merece la pena yo Facebook lo que lo
had was the main page that I
que tenía era la página principal que lo
used to uh
utilizaba para eh
upload a little bit a short upload a
subir un poquito un short subir una
little thing like that but well we have created the
cosita así pero bueno hemos creado las
three pages if it's convenient for you
tres páginas si ustedes os viene bien
because I know that many ladies use it
porque yo sé que muchas señoras utilizan
Look there Lili is putting it up I'm
Mira por ahí Lili lo está poniendo lo
going to pin it okay today I'm not going to  set
voy a fijar vale hoy no voy a poneros
goals for you and I'm not going to set them Oh wait
objetivos ni voy a poneros Ay espera
Sorry today I'm not going to set goals for you or
Perdón hoy no voy a poneros objetivos ni
give you encores or bother you
voy a poneros bises ni voy a dar por
with the box or anything like that
culo con la caja ni nada por el estilo
Because what I want Ho and straight to the point Is for
Porque lo que quiero Ho y a saco Es que
all of you to follow me on the Facebook page
todas me sigáis en la página de Facebook
okay Lili has set the one for
vale Lili ha fijado la de la de
telesalseo okay Lily has set the one for
telesalseo vale Lily ha fijado la de
telesalseo But look here we're
telesalseo Pero mira aquí estamos
uploading all the same videos as on
subiendo todos los mismos vídeos que en
telesalseo okay the same perfectly Okay
telesalseo vale igual perfectamente Okay
and the live shows are going to be done too
y se van a hacer los directos también
but just like there's the telesalseo one
pero al igual que está la de telesalseo
well you have the main one Javi
pues tenéis la la principal la de Javi
Oliveira's also the one for Javi Oliveira
oliveira además la de Javi oliveira la
you're going to find it easy because it's
vasis a encontrar fácil porque está
verified Okay they verified it for me I
verificada Vale me la verificaron me
imagine with Instagram I don't know it's just that I did
imagino que con el Instagram No lo sé es
n't realize when Damn they verified it for me
que no me di cuenta cuándo [__] me la
But anyway
verificaron Pero bueno que
if you want the ideal would be for me to follow
si queréis lo ideal sería que siguiese
the three pages okay the main one
las tres páginas vale la del principal
Javi Oliveira the one for telesalseo
Javi oliveira la de la de telesalseo os
go to Facebook Well you have the
metéis en Facebook Bueno tenéis ahí el
link there okay don't go to Facebook
enlace vale que no os metéis en Facebook
and I wrote telesalseo watch out because there's another one
y escribí telesalseo ojo porque hay otra
page called telesalseo and it's not
página que se llama telesalseo y no es
mine eh watch out because I'm seeing that
mía eh ojo porque estoy viendo que
another page appears that is not mine
aparece otra otra página que no es mía
eh okay mine is the one with the
eh vale la mía es la que tiene el
pepper mine is this one okay the one with
pimiento la mía es esta vale la que
the pepper right now it has 400
tiene el pimiento ahora mismo tiene 400
75 followers okay And since you're
75 seguidores okay Y como ustedes me
going to follow me right now okay all of you
vais a seguir ahora mismo vale todos los
who are here are going to follow me we're going to
que estáis aquí me vais a seguir vamos a
reach 1000 the kids have reached
llegar a 1000 los chavales han llegado a
1000 eh the kids if I'm not mistaken
1000 eh los chavales si no me equivoco
this page is what I'm telling you I mean it doesn't
esta página es lo que os digo O sea no
monetize nor do I think it ever monetizes
monetiza ni creo que monetiza en la vida
okay eh but we have it there more than anything
vale eh pero la tenemos ahí más que nada
okay I have it more than anything for Miguel
vale la tengo más que nada por Miguel
pastrana I have a group with Hey hey
pastrana yo tengo un grupo con Oye oye
Miguel well well have us there the
Miguel pues pues mé tenos ahí las
pages no I mean share us there
páginas no O sea compártenos por ahí la
the page Miguel the telesalseo had you
la página Miguel la de telesalseo habías
thought about streaming in 20 too Well
pensado en streamear en 20 también Pues
look eh Although it sounds like a joke, not
mira eh Aunque os suena cachondeo no el
this thing of opening some
tema este de abrirse unas páginas de
Facebook pages eh Although it sounds like a joke  You
Facebook eh Aunque os suene cachondeo ya
know that we have some rather
sabéis que tenemos gente un tanto
special people behind us okay that they are
especial detrás nuestra vale que están
trying to express themselves without any
intentando manifestados sin ningún tipo
shame and without any kind of cut they
de vergüenza y sin ningún tipo de corte
have not expressed publicly they have
no han manifestado públicamente se han
expressed publicly in several
manifestado públicamente en varios
channels that they want to close my
canales que quieren cerrar me los
channels Okay what is happening yes let's
canales Ok qué es lo que pasa que si a
see I understand that no I hope not I
ver yo entiendo que no Ojalá que no
hope not no but what if suddenly
Espero que no no pero que si de repente
some reports slipped through Maybe later I can get it
colase algunos reportes A lo mejor luego
back I appeal it I fight it I denounce a
lo recupero lo apelo lo peleo denuncio
thousand things no but it is quite likely
mil cosas no pero es bastante probable
that one day I might fail or I get on a
que un día yo tuve falle o yo me coja de
trip and I can't be appealing or these
viaje y no pueda estar apelando o estas
things many things can happen okay
cosas pueden pasar muchas movidas vale
many things can happen and it can
pueden pasar muchas movidas y puede
happen that while you are appealing they
pasar que mientras que estés apelando
have the channels closed no longer it
pues tengan los canales cerrados ya no
happened to me once when they close one
ya me pasó una vez cuando te cierran un
channel they close all the channels
canal te cierran todos los canales
So these people what they want
Entonces esta gente lo que nos quieren
is to leave us without channels Okay they have
es dejar sin canales Ok lo han
expressed it without any kind of cut in
manifestado sin ningún tipo de corte en
several channels okay in space they have also
varios canales vale en space también lo
talked about it I was showing it in the
han hablado lo estuve enseñando en el
video the other day of the main Channel
vídeo del otro día del Canal principal
so it is very important that
entonces muy importante que todo el
everyone always follows us I know I am very
mundo nos siga siempre Sé que soy muy
heavy I know I am very heavy but well I
pesado Sé que soy muy pesado pero bueno
think  that what I'm asking you for doesn't
creo que esto que os estoy pidiendo No
cost any money so no it doesn't cost anything
Cuesta dinero así que no no cuesta nada
okay for you to follow me on everything okay In
vale que que me sigáis en todo vale De
fact in this excerpt Lili we're going to
hecho en este extracto Lili lo vamos a
put it Even in the pinned comment
poner Incluso en en el comentario fijado
in the pinned comment we're going to put the
en el comentario fijado vamos a poner la
page Why Because suddenly tomorrow
página Por qué Porque de repente mañana
you go to YouTube telesalseo doesn't exist and
entráis a YouTube telesalseo no existe y
I'm going to have a statement on
yo os voy a tener un comunicado en
Facebook a statement on my Instagram
Facebook un comunicado En mi Instagram
a statement on my Twitter okay we
un comunicado en mi Twitter vale que
have a lot of people who follow us we
tenemos mucha gente que nos sigue que
have a lot of people who follow us no
tenemos mucha gente que nos sigue no
especially on Twitter we are we are
sobre todo en en Twitter somos somos
incredible what we move on Twitter I'm not going to take
increíble lo que movemos en Twitter no
advantage and I'm going to talk about this in
voy a aprovechar y voy a hailar esto en
this excerpt to comment a little on something
este extracto para comentar un poco algo
that was happening last night we're going to
que estuvo sucediendo anoche vamos a
talk about several topics I have to
hablar de varios temas tengo que
tell you some things about the Daniel
comentaros algunas cosas del caso Daniel
Sancho case of Trium de Ospina but since I
Sancho de trium de ospina pero ya que os
've told you about the
he comentado lo de las páginas de
Facebook pages okay that we have created as a
Facebook vale que hemos creado de
backup in case that may happen okay
repuesto por lo que pueda pasar vale
you guys hit follow me hit the
ustedes darle seguirme darle al botón de
share button so that's what it's like a
compartir para para que es como un
retweet okay
retweet vale
and but last night while we were
e pero anoche mientras que estábamos
here having a laugh in El Corrillo and
aquí echando unas risas en el Corrillo y
such well something happened that the truth is
tal pues sucedía algo que que la verdad
I already  I don't know how to define the truth I do
yo ya no sé cómo Definir la verdad yo ya
n't know how to define okay Thursday night
no sé cómo definir vale noche de jueves
Thursday to Friday no last night
de jueves a viernes no la noche de ayer
at 3 in the morning when I was finishing
a las 3 de la mañana cuando yo terminaba
the salsa they told me come in one
la salsería me avisaron entreé un
moment okay we downloaded it Loli Huertas
momento vale lo descargamos Loli huertas
and Tania Palacio were dancing songs with
Y Tania Palacio bailaban canciones con
puppies that they've made for me with you know
perritos que me han hecho con ya sabéis
Tania well every day as if she were
que Tania pues cada día como si fuera
a Disney villain or something like that she does
una villana de Disney o algo por el
n't make songs for me with cona I mean that's what she does
estilo no me hace canciones cona o sea
now not that Her
se dedica a eso ahora no ese Su
content making songs for me with ia like
contenido hacerme canciones con ía en
Let's fight against you we are the
plan Vamos a luchar contra ti somos los
good guys I don't know what Ricky edy is in charge okay I
buenos no sé qué Ricky edy manda vale o
mean all that stuff that this girl has
sea toda esa movida que esta chica tiene
in her head Okay
en su cabeza Okay
Eh Well nothing last night Loli Huerta jitania
Eh Pues nada anoche Loli Huerta jitania
dedicated themselves at 3 in the morning to
se dedicaron a las 3 de la mañana a
dancing this type of songs songs
bailar este tipo de canciones canciones
about puppies putting a pompadour on a
de perritos poniéndole un tupé a un
puppy to call me a dog to
perrito para llamarme perro para
insult me ​​and to denigrate Okay
insultarme y para denigrar Okay nos lo
Carmen put it on us we went crazy I'm already that it does
puso Carmen nos quedamos locos yo ya a
n't drive me crazy at all ah it doesn't
mí es que no me deja loco nada a no me
surprise me at this point nothing You know I mean
sorprende ya est altura nada Sabes O sea
what  I'm telling you, so this is already a
qué te digo o sea esto ya es actitud de
bully attitude it's a little dog that another
bully est un perrito que creó otro
youtuber created that is dedicated to harassing me okay
youtuber que se dedica a acosarme vale
that he has dedicated himself for a long time
que se ha dedicado durante mucho tiempo
to be able to eat to take something not an
para poder comer para llevar algo no un
extra harass me literally insults
extra acosarme literalmente insultos
very personal things very things I mean it
cosas muy personales cosas muy o sea se
was a youtuber who stood next to the
era un youtuber que se puso al lado el
dog every day every day he
perro todos los días todos los días se
stood next to the dog and imitated how the
ponía el perro al lado y imitaba como el
accent made his mouth move he imitated
acento le hacía mover la boca imitaba
how the Andalusian accent okay And
como el acento andaluz vale Y se ponía
the dog started to say maybe it's me I'm
el perro a decir a lo mejor soy yo soy
Dallas's pet Yeah they've given me
la mascota de Dallas Ja me han dado
think look look I don't know what I mean
pienso mira mira no sé qué O sea
humiliating humiliating humiliating
humillante humillante humillante
humiliating okay But these are the ones from the
humillante vale Pero estos son los de la
fight against harassment it depends it depends it depends
lucha contra el acoso depende Depende
okay I mean this is a real
depende vale o sea esto es de verdadero
bully a real bully because you
bully de verdadero bully porque tú
can criticize you can talk about the
puedes criticar tú puedes hablar de las
people who are famous but man
personas que somos conocidas pero hombre
what I'm telling you is that it's not even a parody it
qué te digo es que no es ni parodia que
's not even a parody Because it's still a
no es ni parodia Porque todavía una
parody still a you know what I'm telling you
parodia todavía una sabes lo que te digo
is that it's not even a parody I mean putting a
es que no es ni parodia o sea poner a un
dog to insult me ​​in all
perro para insultarme de todas las
possible ways And treating the dog in a
maneras posibles Y tratar al perro de
way  humiliating as if I were to
manera humillante como si fuera yo para
report you to report you buddy okay
denunciarte para denunciarte colega vale
Tania is wanting a lawsuit like
Tania está deseando una demanda como
Loli Well I don't know if she is really wanting a
Loli Pues no lo sé si está deseando una
lawsuit but with her story
demanda la verdad pero ya con sus relato
This is even ridiculous okay
Es que esto queda incluso ridículo vale
more ridiculous There are still for example
más ridículo Todavía queda por ejemplo
people like ard de Troya Listen to what
gente como ard de Troya Escuchar lo que
ard de Troya said a while ago to
ha dicho ard de Troya hace un rato para
justify this this that he sees very healthy he
justificar esto esto que el ve muy sano
was on his channel last night with his people
estaba anoche en su canal con su gente
Elisa was there Loli uploaded from what she
estaba Elisa subió Loli por lo que me ha
told me Loli uploaded and Loli well she likes
contado subió Loli y Loli pues le gusta
dancing a lot and says Play music and I
mucho el bailoteo y dice Ponme música y
played a song and it wasn't very good She
le puse una canción y no era muy allá
says But play something else with more energy I do
Dice Pero ponme algo más con más marcha
n't know what And then she has the song
no sé qué Y entonces tiene la canción
This one that I don't remember which one it was one of the ones that
Esta que no me acuerdo cuál era de las
Loli has Loli sorry one of the ones that
que tiene Loli Loli perdón de las que
t has on her channel nothing songs that
tiene t en su canal nada canciones de
Tania has of the ones that
las que tiene Tania de las que tiene
Tania has on her channel you know let's see what they are
Tania en su canal sabes a ver que son
as if Tania were arian music no I
las como si Tania fuera arian music no O
mean nothing one of these songs that
sea nada una canción de esta de las que
Tania has on her channel let's
tiene Tania en su canal vamos a ver un
see a little What kind of songs
vamos a ver un poco Qué tipo de
Tania has on her  channel no
canciones tiene Tania en su canal no
nothing the songs that Tania has
nada las canciones estas que tiene Tania
well Ricky edie strike Tania pm created
pues Ricky edie strike Tania pm creada
with ia the trial of the
con ía el juicio de los
cowards wild cucumber This is that I
cobardes pepino salvaje Esta es que me
thought was
pareció
wonderful this is nor this she did
maravillosa esto es nor esto lo hizo
when it came out the issue of
cuando salió se hizo viral el tema de la
her husband's sentence went viral which is something
sentencia de su marido que es una cosa
that was already in the media that she
que estaba ya en los medios que ella le
gave it diffusion or rather total nonsense
dio difusión o sea sin sentido total
playing with the priv in short the pathetic
jugando con lo priv en fin los patéticos
arguments that you use well
argumentos que te utilizas pues
converted into
convertido en
[Music]
[Música]
songs the minor was the victim of
canciones la menor fue la víctima de de
that procedure listen to me it's that making
ese procedimiento escúchame es que hacer
these types of songs as if you were a
este tipo de canciones como si fueras un
Disney Villain Look at a song by
Villano de Disney Mira una canción del
Corrillo the wig Look Ah look this is this is this is
Corrillo el peluca Mira Ah mira esta es
the song Look the
esta es esta es la canción Mira el
wig
peluca
[Music]
[Música]
sir with so much retouching it's impossible to me it
señor con tanto retoque no se puede a m
's that when they talk about
es que lo cuando hablan de los retoques
my retouching as if I had changed my
míos como si yo me hubiera cambiado la
entire face it freaks me out that what I
cara entera a mí es que me flipa que lo
've done has been to put on hair and
que he hecho ha sido ponerme pelo y
remove some fat from my
quitarme un poco de grasa de los
eyelids I mean it's that when they talk
párpados o sea yo es que cuando hablan
about the retouching it seems that I am you
de los retoques parece que soy
know Ur when I
sabes Ur cuando
logé pas pel
logé pas pel
teedee This is the story of  the Antonia
teedee Este es el relato de la Antonia
who says that I was behind every
que dice que yo iba detrás todos los
day We have to mention Antonia
días Tenemos que mencionar a Antonia
lately But it's not that I
últimamente Pero es que yo no es que
really want to mention her Antonia
quiera mencionarla de verdad Antonia
Forgive me I really love you Antonia
Perdóname de verdad te quiero Antonia de
really deep down I love you but
verdad en el fondo te tengo cariño pero
what do your friends put you in [ __ ] Yesterday it was
que te meten tus amigos [__] Ayer fue
no [ __ ] way today it wasn't and I'm sorry but I don't I don't I I ca
no m kilar hoy no y yo lo siento pero yo
n't defend myself you
no me no me no me puedo no defender me
understand And today it was your friend Tania who
entiendes Y hoy ha sido tu amiga Tania
you meet in person and
con la que quedas en persona y le y
according to her you hand her papers and give her
según ella le entregas papeles y le das
information okay This is the story of the
información vale Este es el relato de la
Antonia that I fell with the enemy who is
Antonia que yo pé con el enemigo que es
Dallas no because Maria didn't pay
Dallas no porque María no me daba
attention to me and how But how Maria didn't
atención y como Pero cómo Que María no
pay attention to me if Maria collaborated
me daba atención si María colaboró
with me I don't even know how many times I have
conmigo yo no sé ni las veces tengo aquí
a lot of here I have look it makes me very sad
un montón de tengo mira me da mucha pena
because I have one of the things
porque tengo una ella una de las cosas
that the lawsuit says is the issue that I
que pone la demanda es el tema de que yo
insinuate that it is a Partner house I don't know
insinuo que es una casa Partner no sé
what and she argues with me about that I don't have a
qué y me discute eso no tengo aquí una
folder here Damn it I hadn't
carpeta Que [__] sea que no la había
found it at the time of delivering it
encontrado en el momento de entregarlo
I have a video that she recorded with me she
tengo vídeo que ella grababa conmigo se
painted here on her forehead Partner house or  I have a
pintaba aquí en la frente casa Partner o
video that she was recording here
sea tengo vídeo que ella grababa aquí
with me I remember a video I have a
conmigo me acuerdo un vídeo tengo un
video where she appears with a red hat
vídeo que sale ella con un gorro rojo
that I asked her for I don't remember what it
que le pedí que no me acuerdo para qué
was for it was also something it was also
era que era algo también de también ha
a joke with the cas panes issue I don't
sido una broma con el tema cas panes no
remember you know but it's like mm at what
me acuerdo sabes pero es como mm en qué
point she didn't pay attention to me I mean yes that
momento no me daba atención o sea si eso
is precisely something that I have always been
es precisamente una cosa que yo siempre
grateful to her that she gave me a
se la he agradecido que ella me dio un
good push a good tug the truth I
buen empujoncito un buen tirón la verdad
mean she collaborated with me having I
O sea ella colaboró conmigo teniendo Yo
almost no followers eh but
casi ni casi nada de Seguidores eh pero
it's like what I'm telling you I mean
es como es lo que te digo o sea es que
this is a lie I didn't go with Dallas
esto es mentira yo no me fui con Dallas
because the other one doesn't give me attention yes yes
porque la otra no me da la atención si
yes we collaborated the biggest we
si si colaboramos lo más grande
collaborated a lot of
colaboramos un montón de
times the one who wants to sue the one who
veces la que quiere demandar la que
wants to sue in this song puts
quiere demandar en esta canción pone
a toupee here
aquí un peluquín
Jen but
el Jen pero
true and it costs you
verdad y te cuesta
you have
tienes
[Music]
[Música]
39 threats with blowing glasses if they touch
39 amenazas con volar gafas si tocan a
your
tu
[Music]
[Música]
people you mess with the family I don't know
gente lo te metes con la familia no sé a
who it
quién se
[Music]
[Música]
refers to that I have fallen apart Well
refiere a que se me ha desmoronado Bueno
I think you have already  I'm a little caught up in what
yo creo que ya habéis pillado un poco de
the songs are about, but
lo que van las canciones cetan no pero
it's like she's the girl, what
es como si estuviera ella la chica qué
mentality does she have because this girl is
mentalidad tiene porque esta tía tiene
my age, no, I mean, of course, this is
mi edad no O sea Claro pues esto que te
done by a kid who is living
lo haga un niño que que está viviendo
like he's the protagonist or the villain of
como que es protagonista o Villano de de
a Disney story, not one of these
un cuento Disney no de una peli de estas
Disney movies, no, where the villain appears, I'll fly, I'll
de Disney no que sale el Villano volaré
fly, you're very bad and when I was a kid you
volaré eres muy malo y cuando chico me
used to tell me, I don't know what, I mean, those are the
decías no sé qué no O sea eso son las
typical Disney songs, not from
típicas canciones estas de Disney no de
Disney musicals, but it covered up,
los musicales de Disney pero como tapaba
man, what the hell is this doing, right? But
tío qu qué [__] hace esto no Pero
anyway, according to Art of Troy, according to Art of
bueno según Art de troyas según ar de
Troy, I don't remember which one he
troyas no me acuerdo cuál es la que me
told me, but it's the one with
ha dicho pero es la que tiene el perro
this dog that you have on screen, it's the
este que tenéis en pantalla que es el
dog that made a mess with the toupee,
perro que hizo un pasado con el peluquín
boo, what I just told you, okay, I
buo lo queos acabo de comentar vale o
mean, pure, pure [ __ ], pure bullying, in
sea puro puro bule puro bullying de
fact, the dog's name is his
hecho se llama el perro se llama
toupee, that pet, and Fabi, well, he
peluquín la mascota esa y el Fabi pues
's really bad, and by the way, unpa started
está mu que por cierto unpa se puso a
saying later that we all have that,
decir luego que eso lo tenemos todos
super, it's just that Gun is doing something, he has one. The thing is, I
super es que gun pasa tiene una Lo que
can't sue  to
pasa que no puedo demandar a todo el
everyone I'm not lazy or know And such But
mundo ni me da pereza ni sab Y tal Pero
the one the one pas what you have a good
el un el un pas lo que tienes un buen
video on the main channel that we've been
vídeo en el canal principal que que
watching this week some
hemos estado viendo esta semana unas
things but the guy then started
cosas pero que el tío se puso luego a
saying when would he check or ask
decir cuando comprobaría o preguntaría
that he has a lawsuit is that he has
que que tiene una demanda es que tiene
a lawsuit let's see one thing that you
una demanda vamos a ver una cosa que tú
do a parody a criticism a such
hagas una parodia una crítica un tal
But you put Every [ __ ] day I don't
Pero tú poner Todos los [__] días no s
know how long it was it was
no sé ni cuánto tiempo fue fueron
weeks or months eh every [ __ ] day to the
semanas o meses eh todos los [__] días
dog next to making reference to
al perro al lado haciendo referencia a
everything that I said yeah look bend down
todo lo que yo decía sí mira agáchate
there get the feed I don't know what Yeah my hair
ahí coge el pienso no sé qué Sí mi pelo
how ugly they've made my hair How
que qué feo me han puesto el pelo Qué
bad is the surgeon not everything all the
malo es el cirujano no todo todo el
time humiliating I don't know what I don't know there are
tiempo humillando no sé qué no sé hay
convictions for that there are convictions of people
condenas por eso hay condenas de gente
who wanted to grab it and there are
que se quería agarrar a la y hay
convictions for that and then a pas started
condenas por eso y luego empezó un pas a
saying that no that he wasn't going after anyone
decir que que no que no iba por nadie
that the dog wasn't going after anyone that good
que el perro no iba por nadie que bueno
that the coincidence if it coincided with something
que la casualidad si coincidía con algo
You know how nervous because to a
Sabes como nervioso porque a un clavo
burning nail to have something to
Ardiendo para tener algo de lo que
talk about Good night Cinta Marquez  from
hablar Buenas noches cinta marquez de
dayamon come back there I have to go
dayamon te vuelva allí tengo yo que ir
someday they say there's bujam eh
algún día dicen que hay bujam eh noche
Thursday to Friday nights it doesn't put
de jueves a viernes no pone en contexto
the boy in context Thursday to Friday nights s It
el muchacho noche de jueves a viernes s
seems to me that s you're going to have to go there
Me parece que s vas a tener que ir all
now Monte 3 in the morning Lolly wer And
ya Monte 3 de la mañana Lolly wer Y
Tania Palacios were dancing songs with
Tania Palacios bailaban canciones con
little dogs that they've made me cona that they've made you that they've
perritos que me han hecho cona que te
made you with ia okay
han hecho que te han hecho con ía vale
little dog that belongs to gumpa the
perrito que pertenece al gumpa la
creation is from gumpa not Tania
creación es de gumpa no de Tania café
iced coffee a kiss and then okay the
con hielo un beso y entonces vale la
radio television Spanish mode radio
radio televisión española modo radio
okay that that's a hint for what
vale eso eso es una indirecta para que
ha Eh well I'll go back with Tania because she
ha Eh bueno vuelvo con la Tania pues
played this song because it has more rhythm
puso esta canción porque tiene más rimmo
and Loli was dancing to it for a while and then she
y Loli estuvo bailándola un rato y luego
sat down and they continued with theirs but from what she
se sentó y siguieron con los suyos per
tells me is that I haven't seen it, I have
lo que me conta es que yo no lo he visto
n't seen it fun Well the
no lo he visto divertido Pues el
boy grabs that Ah he grabs it because it
muchacho se agarra eso Ah se agarra por
seems that he has it Compared to a
se ve que se tiene Comparado con un
dog I don't understand because being
perro yo no lo entiendo porque que te
called a dog is too much for you because
llamen perro a ti te viene grande porque
dogs are good they are faithful they
los perros son buenos son fieles
defend their people and all those things
defienden a su gente y todas esas cosas
are characteristics that you don't have
son características que tú no reúnes
So why do you compare yourself to a
Entonces por qué te comparas con un
dog Ah I compare myself I
perro Ah que yo me comparo que yo me
compare myself to a dog Ah family I
comparo con un perro Ah familia que yo
compare myself to a dog damn it
me comparo con un perro [__] [__] la
's my fault Ah sure but well there is
culpa es mía Ah claro pero bueno hay a
each one but he gets really offended he gets really
cada uno pero él se ofende mucho se
offended because they call him a dog Ah
ofende mucho porque lo llaman perro Ah
ah Hey don't get offended if they call you a dog
ah Oye no te ofendas si te llaman perro
eh No no no don't get offended eh you have to
eh No no no no te ofendas eh que hay que
see that you get offended or if he sees a dog
ver que te ofendes o si ve cu un perro
in any video He already thinks it's
en cualquier vídeo Ya se las da que es
for him no If he sees a dog in any
para él no Si ve un perro en cualquier
video that has a pompadour and that says he
vídeo que tiene un tupé y que dice que
went after Maria and then left with
fue detrás de María y luego se fue con
Dallas and that makes glasses fly or that they
Dallas y que hace volar gafas o que le
file lawsuits of course he takes it as if it's
ponen demandas claro se la da por
alluded to it's not like they are people who
aludido no es como que sean personas que
are every day with your name in their
están tod días con tu nombre en la
mouths they are peculiar let's leave it there
boca son peculiares vamos a dejarlo ahí
by the way No no let's leave it there
por cierto No no vamos a dejarlo ahí
witch how about a kiss today I said it
bruja qué tal un beso hoy lo he dicho
okay I'm not going to
vale no voy a
ask you I'm not going to be asking today I haven't
pediros no voy a estar pidiendo hoy no
set a challenge okay today I haven't set a
he puesto reto vale hoy no he puesto
goal But what I am going to
objetivo Pero lo que sí que os voy a
ask of you all please is the subject of the
pedir a todos por favor es el tema de la
Facebook okay, Lili has left you there,
de Facebook vale os ha dejado ahí Lili
pinned in the chat the page that we have
fijado en el chat la página que tenemos
as a backup in case they throw us out. This okay,
de repuesto por si nos tiran Esto vale
go in and follow the page okay
dle entrad y seguir la página vale
[Music]
[Música]